From 53 overnight, England's only goal on the fourth day was to survive as long as possible on a pitch offering huge and unpredictable turn as well as occasional spitting bounce . Dan Lawrence tried to be proactive, running at Ashwin's first ball to be nutmegged, with Pant completing a spectacular diving stumping. In contrast, Ben Stokes was almost shot-less, tormented by Ashwin in making eight from 51 balls before he offered a bat-pad catch." 	O O O ORG-B O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O PER-B PER-I O O O O O O PER-B O O O O PER-B O PER-B O O O O O O PER-B ORG-B ORG-I O O O O O PER-B O O O O O O O O O O O O 
울 노원구에서 모녀 3명을 살해한 혐의를 받는 25살 남성 김 모 씨의 구속 여부가 오늘(4일) 결정될 것으로 보입니다.
김 씨에 대한 구속영장 심사는 오늘 오후 2시 서울북부지방법원에서 열리는데, 이르면 오후 늦게 구속 여부가 결정될 것으로 예상됩니다.
앞서 김 씨는 지난달 25일 노원구 중계동의 한 아파트에서 모녀 3명을 살해한 혐의로 경찰에 붙잡혔습니다.
불어민주당 박영선·국민의힘 오세훈 서울시장 후보가 선거운동 막판 '2030 세대' 표심 잡기에 공을 들이고 있다. 젊은 유권자들의 지지가 전체 선거의 승패를 좌우할 것으로 보고, 박 후보는 막판 뒤집기 전략, 오 후보는 판세 굳히기 전략 차원에서 이들에 경쟁적으로 구애하는 모습..."	O O O ORG-B O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O PER-B PER-I O O O O O O PER-B O O O O O O PER-B O O O O O O PER-B ORG-B ORG-I O O O O O PER-B O O O O O O O O O O O O